okay so what is the plan um as you know
I change my mind about things all the
time but I wanted to keep people up to
dat so if they want to kind of tune in
and know what's going on you can kind of
follow along so here is the latest
schedule um we've been doing the coffee
boost uh from 9:00 to 10: in the morning
it's just music and random calendar
review going answering questions of that
people have about technical issues or
whatever uh it's kind of a Morning Show
it's been really fun um we have the
beginner boost on Saturdays 10 to 2ish
it kind of goes long sometimes and
that's why there's no IRL activity
planned other than yoga on that day um
but a couple of things that I wanted to
point out that are totally new now these
are things that that that are going to
give some structure around some some
other things so a lot of you know um I'm
really big into biking at least I have
been it's been one of the main things
I've been doing IRL and I've been biking
for three to five hours a day every day
for as long as I mean even in the
thunderstorm but for the most part uh
for a long time so people have been
wondering where is the biking and how
can I know when to find it so um I'm
going to try this I'm going to try to
put on the calendar uh when mountain
biking is going to be which is Mondays
and Fridays and that's from 4:00 to 7:
you'll notice there's not as many hours
of this kind of stuff is now because I'm
not uh I'm not needing as much of it I'm
not preparing in for some sort of ultra
endurance event I'm just maintaining my
health um so you'll see that the number
of hours for for outdoor activity and
and stuff is has gone down I'm still I'm
still outside on on an average of three
two to three hours a day doing different
things but the the point is that this is
hopefully going to be uh so if you want
to take part in mountain biking um you
know Mondays and Fridays I'm going to
shoot to do mountain biking on Mondays
and Fridays I'm going to shoot to do uh
paddle board ing uh probably in Jon Park
every time on Tuesdays and Thursdays uh
these are very very chill streams when I
do paddle boarding I don't I'm not like
grunting through and paddling as hard as
I can I'm paddling for kind of
relaxation and it's usually out in
nature and we try to make it as relaxing
as possible there's no music in any of
these but um but that if if you like
just seeing nature and you just want a
chill paddle stream that would be the
time to come check in um people have
been pushing for paddle stream for a
long time
um I am actually attempting to make a a
paddle stream where the camera is not
attached to my body I'm actually working
on that um I'm working on a way to
attach the the camera to the front of
the paddle board so that I don't have to
have stuff on my back I don't I don't
like to wear a lot of gear when I'm on
the paddle board uh plus if I were to
fall in uh you know the gear would still
be largely safe so so stay tuned for
that if you want to see how that going
uh the assault was replaced with Crispy
creams it was indeed it was much more
fun um so the road biking that I used to
do every day uh the goblin route is now
Wednesdays and Sundays and if you
haven't noticed um uh if you go to straa
and you go to the goblin route it's
changed significantly it's now only
50k um I've chopped a lot of stuff off
of the route um and you can go to my
straa strava.com rvx Rob if you really
want to you can go look up the route and
into the ploh power no we are not going
to no we're not going to do that no Siri
so so here is the new
Goblin um uh it's actually one of the
reasons you might like it is because it
does um
include uh it's it's it's much more
Scenic it's got more Trails on it um I
will do it probably about a I want to
I'm going to shoot for maybe a 2 4 km
per hour Pace uh so I'll be finishing
this in about 2 hours it says say 2
hours 31 minutes but that's probably
because we'll we'll take we'll probably
take a beer Break um not every time but
we'll take some sort of break when we do
when we do goblin so that is the plan um
that we'll be doing the same Goblin
route on Wednesdays and Sundays when
there should be very little traffic but
a lot of activity outside at at burkdale
and um and then we will be doing nothing
on Saturday so Saturday afternoon I'll
probably be making videos uh if not
recovering from these big long streaming
sessions which take a lot of energy out
of me actually um and that's it so the
yoga at the yoga at the end of the day
every day um I'm I'm very ambitious I I
want to really try to get back to Daily
Yoga um I'm not going to plan it uh you
know a moonay or a day off like they do
with the stronger tradition um if I were
to take that day off it would probably
be on a Saturday but I'm still going to
try to do yoga every day there's nothing
there's nothing that says you have to do
yoga every day or you don't want to do
yoga every day the only reason I want to
do that because I really want to get
into the habit of doing it and I I like
being outside when there's when there's
set that going out how you doing Tri so
so that that's the plan if you if you
want to join me for that schedule we'd
love to have you thanks